screenprinting.com 2004-11-30

# Screenprinting.com: screen printing, embroidery, custom t-shirts, custom tshirts, custom t shirts, t-shirt screen printing, tshirt embroidery, t shirt embroidery! Design your own!

**Information**  

|  |  |  **Contact Us**  
Contact Us  
About Us  
Employment  
Hats  
|  |  **Your Account**  
Membership  
Legal Info |  |    
|  |    
  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
**Privacy Statement**  

At Screenprinting.com, we are committed to protecting your privacy and we acknowledge that you may have concerns regarding the use of personal information. With our statement, we intend to explain how we use the information we have gathered from our visitors or members. 

Personally identifiable information is information that identifies you as an individual, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, credit card information and password. We may collect Personally Identifiable Information from you when you make a purchase, register to become a member, voluntarily provide it when you use the site, disclose it in a public area of the site (such as submitting a quote or newsletter request) or provide it when you communicate with us. 

Non-personally identifiable information is information that does not identify you as an individual. Non-Personally Identifiable Information includes information such as your browser type, the URL of the previous Web site you visited, the Web pages and advertisements you view or select, and the types of services you use. 

At Screenprinting.com, we gather and store certain types of information you provide to us through our website, surveys, or other data gathering methods. This information includes contact, demographic and financial information. We use the contact and demographic information to communicate effectively with you and to create a more personalized shopping experience. We may also use the Personally Identifiable Information you provide to administer and manage your account, pay commissions to you, include you on mailing lists and advertise and promote our services. In addition, we may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information when we believe in good faith that it is required by any applicable law or legal process, or if we believe we need to disclose it to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of our members, users, or other third parties. Without limitation of the foregoing, we may disclose your information pursuant to our Intellectual Property Rights Policy to a third party that alleges you have infringed their intellectual property rights. 

We may disclose Non-Personally Identifiable Information in connection with improving the services we offer and facilitating our marketing efforts. In addition, we may combine your Non-Personally Identifiable Information that relates to your use of the Site with that of other users to determine which areas of the Site are most popular, and how our services are used. By collecting this Aggregate Information and analyzing it, we can use it to improve the Site. We may disclose Aggregate Information in connection with improving the services we offer and facilitating our marketing efforts. 

Cookies are information files that are placed on the hard drive of your computer by your browser. Cookies allow websites to remember users activities and visits to a site. At Screenprinting.com, we use cookies to determine the number of unique visitors we host on our website over any given period of time. Cookies are also used to remember user screen names so multiple logins are not necessary. We do not use cookies to store or gather personal information from our visitors. You can disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. For more about cookies see [[http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/)]. 

Screenprinting.com is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To help prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We use encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. Preventing credit card fraud is important to protect your personal financial data security. 

Screenprinting.com does not sell products for purchase by children but we do sell children’s products for purchase by adults. In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), if you are under the age of 13, you may use Screenprinting.com only with involvement of a parent or guardian. We encourage children to involve their parents in any interactive activity they participate in online. We will not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children we know to be under the age of thirteen. In addition, once we are notified we will delete any information in our databases that originates from a child under the age of thirteen. 

Although we will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of your information, transmissions on the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Accordingly, we assume no responsibility or liability for disclosure of any of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access or other causes beyond our reasonable control. 

In an effort to enhance your shopping experience, we may use your contact and demographic information we have collected through our website, surveys, or other data gathering methods to send you news, offers and e-mails from some of our partners. To opt out of receiving news, offers and e-mails [click here]. 

As a part of our business relationships, we may from time to time have banner or link redirects to a third party accessible from the Screenprinting.com Site. Any transactions that occur between you and a third party are strictly between you and the third party and are not the responsibility of Screenprinting.com. We do not control the privacy policies of our advertisers or other third parties that have Web sites linked to the Site. If you click on an advertisement or link, the privacy policies of the Web site that you link to will govern the use of your information by that Web site's operator. We assume no responsibility or liability for the actions of such third parties with respect to their use of your information or otherwise. 

As our company grows, there is a possibility that we could be sold to another company. In the event that we are acquired by another company or a significant portion of our assets is sold to another company, all of the customer information including both financial records and consumer information that we have collected may be transferred to the new company. 

If you do not wish to receive announcements or special offers from us or third parties, you can [click here] to unsubscribe from receiving e-mail communications regarding news, exclusive offers and reminders. 

If you use the Site, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and we will have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to have your information used in any of the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of the Site. Use of this site is when this privacy effective date begins. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Site after we either personally notify you or generally post such changes on the site will constitute your acceptance of those changes.
